Shibuya
Now that's more like it, puppet master!
That's right.
My victory condition is Satoru Gojo.
I have to use any means
necessary to get in contact
with Satoru and tell him
about the Shibuya plot.
Then I'll have him protect me.
But even if I want to focus on Code,
the one who lowered this veil,
Mahito is too dangerous to ignore.
I'll have to exercise him first.
Charge! One year!
Burn him now! Mechamaru!
Hold your cannon!
Are you planning to keep burning me
until you run out of cursed energy?
I'll start by drawing you out!
Get out of here where I'm coming in!
You are my special.
You are
my special.
Now what do you want to do?
I'll show you what you want to do
Say, gay.
I love you, baby.
We're gonna sing the song.
We're gonna sing it.
Where do we go?
I just trust you.
We're gonna sing the song.
Let's kiss you.
Yong, shut down, shut down.
Didn't I ever give up?
You don't? Never give up.
One time.
You're all around.
But I am so real but you are my special.
So we see me on our ride.
We shall make you cry your
own but you are my only one.
And we are my special.
We are special
Mechamaru's attacks won't be
able to damage Mahito's soul.
I'm sure he's aware of that as well.
Charge!
Two years!
Miracle Tanner!
I guess you won't break off your attack.
And you're not paying my
attacks any heed now either.
Just where I want you.
That's when I shoot you with this.
He has so much power!
If I wait, he'll break my armor!
Alright, I have four chances!
I'll try to end this quickly!
Get target in your sights!
And fire!
Mechamaru!
There's no points haven't
you been paying attention
What's going on here?
Was my soul destroyed too?
Another bird for a bad imagination.
The left arm I blew away is regenerated?
No.
He's just tweaking the shape of his soul
to make it look like it regenerated.
The fact that he's showing
it off is proof of that.
It's alright.
I'll show him he's not fooling me!
It is affecting him.
He's not doing badly.
It might be temporary, but his cursed
energy output is special grade class.
He's fully prepared to
deal with Mahito too.
Depending on how this goes
this could be the moment I get
Charge five years?
Pagin
Let's go.
I can't tell which of his attacks
will actually affect my soul.
I need to know that
before I can do anything.
Oh, I can do this!
That'd be groovy.
I can win!
I'll be able to see...
everyone!
Domain Expansion
Self-embodiment of perfection
And you're done.
Idle Transfiguration.
It doesn't matter if I touch you directly
or not once you're inside my domain.
But you already understood that, right?
He got me that curse
technique is sealed in these
although it was the only way
i was going to be able to
manage this technique there's
only 10 days left until
halloween do you think that
meant i'd hold back my cursed
energy and avoid using my
domain give me 10 days and
i'll make a full recovery i
have two left in stock this
was devised in the Heian era
an era full of fierce cursed
spirits and curse users when
Jujutsu was at its height
created by Sadatsu no Ashiya
to protect his disciples
don't incorporate hopes and
dreams into your strategy i
feel so bad for you i I don't
know whether to gloat or not.
It was passed down in his school.
And a pact forbade his students from
conveying that technique to anyone else.
It's a means for them to protect
themselves from others' domains.
A domain for the weak.
Uh-huh
New shadow style simple domain
He used the simple domain, but domain
neutralizes all other techniques,
attacks will end, even
on Satoru Gojo when they're made within
a domain, even if it's a simple one,
activating it
inside a domain would definitely damage
Mahito, regardless of any techniques.
No more spectating from
the sidelines for you!
Suguru Code!
What a happy miscalculation!
I still have one simple domain and
nine years of cursed energy left!
I can fight, Suguru Code!
I can win!
I'll be able to see everyone!
I failed to finish him off.
Come out!
Mechamaru
I still have one domain left.
I'll ram it directly into him!
Here we go, Mechamaru!
Yeah!
Hey, Mechamaru.
Is it okay if I pay you
a visit sometime soon?
Since the exchange event, and
since the baseball game too,
I feel like we've all become
closer friends to each other.
Maybe it's because we all
work as Jujutsu sorcerers,
but I feel like there was always distance
between us, even when we all got along.
I suppose that's because being too close
would make it even more
painful when we died.
But that's changed now.
I love how close we've all become.
Oh, you couldn't quite play in
the baseball game, remember?
So you had a pitching machine
take your place on the mound.
But here's the truth.
I want to get closer to you, Mechamaru.
I mean it.
So one day, I'll come to see you.
That was a bit dangerous
for you, wasn't it?
I made myself burst apart at the same
instant that he activated his technique.
Undoing my domain after that
would make him think I was dead.
It was all calculated.
Not dangerous at all.
So that was another
use of a simple domain.
Good thing we got to see
it before the main event.
Yeah.
I was able to finish adjusting
the entrusted veil as well.
There won't be any problems with entrusting
the cursed energy enchant to others.
Just after 7 p .m.
on October 31, 2018, a roughly
Metro radius veil was lowered,
centered around Tokyo
Department Store's Tokyo Outlet.
Do you need some more drinks?
I love you.
I heard that a lot of people
are coming in for Halloween,
all the way from Ibaraki and Tojigi.
Whoa, from out there?
Excuse me, can I get a picture with you?
Yeah, you're really cute.
Sure. Thanks a lot. Glad to.
This is crazy.
Let's not do Shibuya again next year.
What's that?
What's what?
That, right there in the sky.
I don't see anything.
I'm telling you, it's right there.
Just how many drinks have you had tonight?
What are you doing down there?
What an idiot.
It's too early to be that drunk.
I'm telling you, there's a wall there.
Woo-hey! Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go!
It's a veil that traps
only regular people inside,
and only regular people
are able to enter it.
Sorcerers and assistant supervisors
are able to come and go.
And the signal?
It remains blocked.
Please use assistant supervisors like us,
or first exit the veil
in order to communicate.
Want to know something?
This has become an awfully big problem.
Bushigoro! Bushigoro!
Did you know that when
a sorcerer adds more
effects to the barrier
of an existing veil,
basically, you can only apply
them to things with cursed energy.
That covers people, cursed spirits
and cursed objects, stuff like that.
So blocking cell phone signals is just
a side effect of a veil being lowered.
That you can't integrate the surrounding
signal directly into a
veil's existing barrier.
Oh, yeah, I knew that.
Look, Eino, he's a very talented man, so
keep the senior act in check, will ya?
What do you mean, Naomi?
You're not acting!
Moving on.
Has anyone told Gojo?
No one's here?
At the scramble crossing
in front of the station?
In Shibuya on Halloween?
It would seem something has happened.
Everyone who came running up to the edge
of the veil to escape said the same thing.
they all yelled bring satoru
gojo why there's no way
any non-sorcerers could
possibly know his name they're
being forced to say that
can't break the veil huh
we're having a hard time with
it the veil isn't actually
preventing any sorcerers
from entering or leaving just
aren't able to break it by
force yet it'll be much faster
to find out who lowered it and
then go take out That curse
user then I suppose it's our
duty to help out with that
No, you are all going to
wait right here on standby
They lowered an advanced barrier and
called out Satoru Gojo by name These
are likely the same culprits behind
the attack during the exchange event.
The upper brass wants to minimize
casualties So they decided
it's best to send Satoru Gojo
in to restore order in Shibuya.
We're all here on
standby outside the veil.
That includes us, Kento Nanami,
Old Man Zenin, and Mei Mei.
They expect us to get
any of Gojo's rebounds.
We won't be able to stay in
contact once we're inside the Veil.
When they say minimize casualties,
they mean sorcerer casualties, right?
They don't care about
casualties among regular people?
Don't get all bristly with me.
Unlike last year's Night Parade
of 100 Demons on Christmas,
plans were already in motion.
I happen to think this is the best call.
Besides, I had myself a little
sneak peek inside the veil earlier.
And things seemed pretty peaceful.
Some people panicked, but no cursed spirits
or curse users were trying to kill them.
The biggest problem is those
regular people are trapped inside.
Though honestly, I don't want to
go back in that veil anytime soon.
And why is that?
Well, it was in Hakari, I think.
Most likely, there's lots of
special-grade cursed spirits underground.
What's going on?
Why can't we pass through here?
You better hurry up and
bring us Satoru Gojo!
Who's this Gojo guy? Huh?
Don't know, but we were told we
can't get out unless he comes here.
Who said that? I don't know! Everyone!
I thought guys weren't supposed
to panic at times like these.
Well, being trapped is like
something out of a horror film.
But we're not really in
that much trouble, right?
By now, somebody's called for help.
But we have no signal.
Did you not see what happened earlier?
Sucked into the air.
That's what happened to the people
who got in the intersection.
Like they were water going
down a bathtub drain.
If I hadn't seen that, I'd be
going home on the train too.
So why don't you use your brain
a little bit, you dumb fucks?
Huh?
Then how about you tell us how
smart people can pass through?
How?
Oh, sorry.
Thank you.
I told you to go buy melon bread but
this is It's chocolate chip melon bread!
Obviously it's way better
with chocolate chips!
They're as different as fried
taters and Gundam models!
Huh?
What's taters?
Next time, the Shibuya incident.
You know what they are, right?
I built an AC model before.